(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Paging Dr.
Cutie Pie!
(Sheldon:)I must say, Amy,
I was very impressed
(Sheldon:)to see that Bernadette got
her PhD.
(Amy:)It's indeed admirable.
(Amy:)Although, it is...
microbiology.
(Sheldon:)Your doctorate is in
neurobiology.
(Sheldon:)I fail to see the distinction.
(Amy:)I'll make it simple for you.
(Amy:)I study the brain,
the organ responsible for
Beethoven's Fifth Symphony.
(Amy:)Bernadette studies yeast,
(Amy:)the organism responsible
for Michelob Lite.
(Amy:)Is there something wrong
with your neck?
(Sheldon:)It's a little stiff.
(Sheldon:)What a remarkably fragile
structure
(Sheldon:)to support
such a valuable payload.
(Sheldon:)Not unlike balancing a Faberge
egg on a Pixie Stick.
(Amy:)Have you considered massage?
(Sheldon:)I'd like to respond
to that sarcastically:
(Sheldon:)Yes, I relish the thought
of a stranger covering my body
(Sheldon:)with oil and rubbing it.
(Amy:)I was proposing you massage your
muscles with your own hands.